<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<autosettings>
 <group name="Server">
  <setting name="LocalHostname" type="string" default="127.0.0.1">
Local hostname to bind the listening socket to. Quite everytime you don't need
to change the default from 127.0.0.1.
  </setting>
  <setting name="LocalPort" type="uint16" default="2593">
Local port to bind the listening socket to. Quite everytime you don't need to
change the default from 2593.
  </setting>
  <setting name="RACPort" type="uint16" default="2594">
Local port to bind the rac listening socket to. Quite everytime you don't need to
change the default from 2594.
  </setting>
  <setting name="MULFilesPath" type="string" default="">
Path where the MUL files are. If set to an empty string (default) it will be
read from the registry (under windows) or it will use the Hypnos' share
directory (under unix-like environments).
  </setting>
  <setting name="EnabledBookSystem" type="flag" default="on" flag="is">
Set this to on if you want the book system to be enabled. If book system is not
enabled, the books aren't writable or readable.
  </setting>
  <setting name="EnabledTradeSystem" type="flag" default="on" flag="is">
Set this to on if you want the Trade system to be enabled. If trade system is not 
enabled, pgs can't trade items with each others.
  </setting>
  <setting name="EnabledBountySystem" type="flag" default="on" flag="is">
Set this to on if you want the Bounty System to be enabled. If bounty system is not
enabled, pgs can't ask for the head of the PK
  </setting>
  <setting name="EnabledPopupHelp" type="flag" default="on" flag="is">
Set this to on if you want the PopupHelp to be enabled. (since t2a)
  </setting>
  <setting name="EnabledUOAssist" type="flag" default="on" flag="is">
Set this to on if you want the UOAssist use to be allowed.
  </setting>
  <setting name="AllowedAssistVersion" type="uint32" default="" flag="get">
Allowed version of UOAssist
  </setting>
  <setting name="MaximumPCs" type="uint8" default="5" flag="get">
The maximum numbers of character an account can handle. 
  </setting>
  <setting name="PlayersDeletePCs" type="flag" default="on" flag="can">
Set this to on if you want the players to be allowed to delete their characters.
  </setting>
  <setting name="BankMaxItems" type="uint16" default="0" flag="get">
The maximum number of items a player can store in his bank.
  </setting>
  <setting name="MaximumItemsOnTile" type="uint8" default="" flag="get">
The maximum number of items in a single world tile.
  </setting>
  <setting name="MaximumSoldItems" type="uint16" default="50" flag="get">
The maximum number of different item stacks sellable in a single session.
  </setting>
  <setting name="InstantGuards" type="flag" default="off" flag="has">
Set this on if you want the Guards to instantly teleport over new criminals.
  </setting>
  <setting name="ShowPCNames" type="flag" default="on" flag="should">
Set this on if you want the characters' names to be shown on single click.
  </setting>
  <setting name="DecayTimer" type="uint32" default="300" flag="get">
The time before a corpse is removed.
  </setting>
  <setting name="WeightPerStr" type="uint32" default="4" flag="get">
The weight a character can carry with one strenght point.
  </setting>
  <setting name="NewbiesGold" type="uint16" default="300" flag="get">
The amount of gold pieces a new character get.
  </setting>
 </group>
 
 <group name="MsgBoards">
  <setting name="MaxPosts" type="uint16" default="128" flag="get">
The maximum possible posts on a message board.
  </setting>
  <setting name="MaxEntries" type="uint16" default="256" flag="get">
The maximum number of entries in ESCORTS.
  </setting>
  <setting name="MessageRetention" type="uint8" default="30" flag="get">
The maximum number of days a post remains on the board.
  </setting>
  <setting name="EscortInitExpire" type="uint32" default="86400" flag="get">
The number of seconds until an escorting quest expires. (Default: 1 day)
  </setting>
  <setting name="EscortActiveExpire" type="uint32" default="1800" flag="get">
Don't know actually. (Default: 1/2 hour)
  </setting>
 </group>
 <group name="Hunger">
  <setting name="Enabled" type="flag" default="on" flag="is">
Set this on if you want the Hunger System to be Enabled.
  </setting>
  <setting name="HungerRate" type="uint16" default="6000" flag="get">
The number of seconds before the character gets hungrier.
  </setting>
  <setting name="HungerDamage" type="uint16" default="2" flag="get">
The number of HP a character loses when is starving.
  </setting>
  <setting name="HungerDamageRate" type="uint16" default="10" flag="get">
The rate a character loses HP when starving. (in seconds)
  </setting>
 </group>
 
 <group name="Actions">
  <setting name="EquipOnDClick" type="flag" default="on" flag="should">
Set this on if you want items to be equipped on double click.
  </setting>
  <setting name="UseItemsWhenInvisible" type="flag" default="off" flag="can">
Set this on to allow people to use items while they are invisible (due to a spell). 
  </setting>
  <setting name="ObjectsDelay" type="uint32" default="2" flag="get">
Delay between the use of two objects. (in seconds)
  </setting>
  <setting name="BandageDelay" type="uint32" default="6" flag="get">
Delay between the use of two bandages. (in seconds)
  </setting>
 </group>
 
 <group name="Skills">
  <setting name="StatDailyLimit" type="uint16" default="" flag="get">
The maximum stat gain in a (real) day.
  </setting>
  <setting name="LimitPlayerSparring" type="uint16" default="0" flag="get">
The number of points the defending player need to have over the attacker to have the attacker gaining skill points. (in PvP only)
  </setting>
  <setting name="MaximumSkillTraining" type="uint16" default="300" flag="get">
The maximum skill an npc can teach to a character.
  </setting>
  <setting name="EnabledSkillBySkillCap" type="flag" default="on" flag="is">
Set this on if you want to allow server side support for clients' skillcap settings.
  </setting>
  <setting name="SkillDelay" type="uint32" default="5" flag="get">
Delay between the use of two skills.
  </setting>
  
  <setting name="StealthOnHorse" type="flag" default="off" flag="can">
Set this on if you want a character to be able to use stealth while on horse.
  </setting>
  <setting name="StealthToTakeItemsWhileHid" type="uint16" default="960" flag="get">
Stealth Skill necessary to pick up an item and  remain hidden.
If INVALID pc is always unhidden while picking up items from the ground.
  </setting>
  <setting name="StealthToDropItemsWhileHid" type="uint16" default="960" flag="get">
Stealth Skill necessary to drop an item and  remain hidden.
If INVALID pc is always unhidden while dropping items on the ground.
  </setting>
  <setting name="MaxStealthStep" type="uint8" default="10" flag="get">
The maximum amount of steps a character can make with stealth until he becomes visible again.
  </setting>
  
  <setting name="SnoopDelay" type="uint32" default="15" flag="get">
The minimum number of seconds between snoops.  
  </setting>
 </group>
 
</autosettings>
