<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<autosettings>
 <group name="Server">
  <setting name="LocalHostname" type="string" default="127.0.0.1">
Local hostname to bind the listening socket to. Quite everytime you don't need
to change the default from 127.0.0.1.
  </setting>
  <setting name="LocalPort" type="uint16" default="2593">
Local port to bind the listening socket to. Quite everytime you don't need to
change the default from 2593.
  </setting>
  <setting name="RACPort" type="uint16" default="2594">
Local port to bind the rac listening socket to. Quite everytime you don't need to
change the default from 2594.
  </setting>
  <setting name="MULFilesPath" type="string" default="">
Path where the MUL files are. If set to an empty string (default) it will be
read from the registry (under windows) or it will use the Hypnos' share
directory (under unix-like environments).
  </setting>
  <setting name="EnabledBookSystem" type="flag" default="on" flag="is">
Set this to on if you want the book system to be enabled. If book system is not
enabled, the books aren't writable or readable.
  </setting>
  <setting Name="EnabledTradeSystem" type="flag" default="on" flag="is">
Set this to on if you want the Trade system to be enabled. If trade system is not 
enabled, pgs can't trade items with each others.
  </setting>
  <setting Name="EnabledBountySystem" type="flag" default="on" flag="is">
Set this to on if you want the Bounty System to be enabled. If bounty system is not
enabled, pgs can't ask for the head of the PK
  </setting>
  <setting Name="EnabledPopupHelp" type="flag" default="on" flag="is">
Set this to on if you want the PopupHelp to be enabled. (since t2a)
  </setting>
  <setting Name="EnabledUOAssist" type="flag" default="on" flag="is">
Set this to on if you want the UOAssist use to be allowed.
  </setting>
  <setting Name="AllowedAssistVersion" type="uint32" default="" flag="get">
Allowed version of UOAssist
  </setting>
  <setting Name="MaximumPCs" type="uint8" default="5" flag="get">
The maximum numbers of character an account can handle. 
  </setting>
  <setting Name="PlayersDeletePCs" type="flag" default="on" flag="can">
Set this to on if you want the players to be allowed to delete their characters.
  </setting>
  <setting Name="BankMaxItems" type="uint16" default="0" flag="get">
The maximum number of items a player can store in his bank.
  </setting>
  <setting Name="MaximumItemsOnTile" type="uint8" default="" flag="get">
The maximum number of items in a single world tile.
  </setting>
 </group>
</autosettings>
